dailygrocerycoupon.com 2019-07-23

# privacy policy | DailyGroceryCoupon

**DailyGroceryCoupon.com Privacy Policy.   **

Last Updated: June 1, 2017

This Privacy Policy is intended to provide you, the user, with a clear explanation of how we obtain, use and retain information you provide to us.

Active Information We Collect  
The personally identifiable information you choose to share with us is optional. When you register on DailyGroceryCoupon.com as a user, you are voluntarily providing us with personal information. This can include your name, email address, postal address, and other information you may decide to share with us. You may also provide us with information by participating in a contests or sweepstakes, polls, and surveys implemented by DailyGroceryCoupon.com or any of its partner sites, or if you voluntarily send us inquiries or messages. We may use this information to contact you regarding possible changes to our site, new services, limited time offers, newsletters, and other information we think you may find useful.

Passive Information Collected  
A ‘cookie’, a small unit of data stored on your computer, is a common feature of web browser software (e.g. Firefox, Safari, Chrome, etc). The “cookie” allows web servers to recognize a particular computer used to access a site. DailyGroceryCoupon utilizes this “cookie” technology, along with third parties, to determine how you use the site. Possible passive information collected during the course of your visit may include your internet service provider, operating system, browser type, date and time of your visit, pages viewed and time spent at our site. DailyGroceryCoupon, along with third parites, are also able to ascertain information through customer tracking which allows us to make certain that your experience using our site is optimized and successful. 

Information Released As a Result of Legal Requirement  
DailyGroceryCoupon.com may be required to disclose information to law enforcement or government agencies for investigation purposes or to resolve legal disputes. To prevent illegal activity and/or potential situations regarding the physical safety of any person, and to protect the safety of our users, personal information may be released to the appropriate agencies.

International Users  
This website is managed and operated in the United States. Any user who uses DailyGroceryCoupon.com outside the jurisdiction of the United States may do so at their own risk, and are personally obligated to comply with local law and regulations. Any user that is not a resident of the United States understands and permits DailyGroceryCoupon.com to acquire and store personal information outside your home jurisdiction.

Persons Under the Age of 13 Are Prohibited From Use  
Any person under the age of 13 is not permitted to use DailyGroceryCoupon.com. The services provided by DailyGroceryCoupon.com are not intended to be utilized by children under the age of 13, and we do not knowingly allow these young users to register on our website.

Business Transfer Statement  
DailyGroceryCoupon.com, at any given time, may fall under new management and ownership through merger or acquisition. If this happens, the successor company will become the lawful owners of all information previously collected by DailyGroceryCoupon.com including account information. However, the successor company will be bound by the standards listed in this Privacy Policy. Such transfers of ownership will be publicly shared, and such information will be available to you through this Privacy Policy.

Comments and Shopping Tips  
Any information submitted to DailyGroceryCoupon.com, including comments, questions, coupons or shopping tips, is considered voluntary. With your submission, you agree that you understand that this information is being shared publicly. DailyGroceryCoupon.com is not responsible for the unauthorized use of this information, and we are not responsible if you receive unsolicited messages.

Changes to Privacy Policy  
If changes are made to this Privacy Policy, we will reflect the changes made by renewing the effective date. DailyGroceryCoupon.com reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time throughout the duration of its existence. Revisions will always be posted publicly.

Questions/Comments/Contact  
If you have any questions or comments, please submit them to: DailyGroceryCoupon Support Team <[Support@DailyGroceryCoupon.com](mailto:Support@DailyGroceryCoupon.com)>
